Thank you for watching
me
Deliver my heart and brother present to you!
Ohhhh!
The members of the show have created their own presents for Bananaman, whose birthday is in April/May, with a budget of 5,000 yen.
So Bananaman will receive a present from his cute little sisters if his guess is wrong, he will buy the present with his own money.
So, it's fine if you do... we're having a birthday party. Last time we got presents from 5 people and missed twice.
Tonight, let's see if we can capture the members' thoughts.
Let's do it!
Oh, here it comes!
Oh, no!
That was close, though.
What?
I used to have one of these.
I can do it like this.
A reissue of this is coming out and it's really popular.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
The baseball version, the one or two years ago.
This is great.
Oh!
Oh, wow.
Oh, my God.
- Oh, my God! - I'm gonna get some kills.
- Oh! Oh! - Seriously.
- Oh! - Fun. Fun.
- Fun. Fun.
- Out.
- Baseball board and what's this?
- Baseball board and what's this one?
- Try a little more.
- This is great!
- I wanted it at my friend's house, but it was at mine.
- This is from when we were kids, right?
- I remember when we were kids.
- I was just reporting this.
- How did you do that?
You can go all the way over here.
I'm not sure if I'll be able to do it again next time.
You know it so well... you know it so well... the next time it's hard... the next time it's not... the next time it's this...
I'll have to do it like this and win right away... or else I'll fall off the grid.
This is fun.
Scary, scary.
That's good.
Which one is it?
Yes, yes.
Uh-oh.
Oh, no.
Is that one of the pans?
That's funny.
It's fun, isn't it?
Athletic game with a baseball version of a nostalgic game
Athletic game
I was too worried about why you would be happy with it, so I talked to my parents about it.
I was so worried about what they would like.
I thought they would enjoy a nostalgic game.
I don't know about this.
We both love this stuff.
What's with all the details? Is it some kind of nonstop?
This was nonstop.
Maybe your parents watched it?
But I think you're more of a baseball fan.
You've said that.
That's true.
But I'm not the one who says "yueh" in this kind of thing.
It's me.
People who go all out with this...
They'll be doing this forever.
Your parents picked you.
Aww...
Like that.
Yeah.
This is fun.
I've seen something like that.
It's been reissued recently, and it's really popular.
I see.
What's that? You've been doing it nonstop?
What?
No, I know a lot about it.
Your parents saw it on TV.
And your parents saw it on TV and had a huge reaction.
I see.
Mr. Hitara... the baseball version... you were nonstop.
The baseball version of the WBC... nonstop.
It was nonstop.
You're watching it, aren't you?
Oh, me.
Okay, then.
No, it wasn't me.
But let me tell you something deeper.
Let's say you're watching nonstop.
They have a little tournament with the performers.
"If you win, you get the baseball version.
I won.
So if you've been watching that...
I'm sure you know that I got this.
Now it's decided!
It's me!It's me!
It's definitely me!
No, you know what, while I'm saying this.
I still think your parents watch Bananaman's show.
I know, because it's a show with Bananaman, who my daughter is always indebted to.
I'm thinking it would be terrible if we were in an area where Non-Stop isn't on.
I know, there are some areas where Non-Stop isn't on.
A few, right?
It's Mr. Himura.
I think it's me.
I think it's Mr. Himura, too.
I think it's good. It's straight. It's me.
Okay, let's go.
I'm the big brother who gets this present. I'm Himura.
Now, who prepared these presents for you?
Yes, sir.
Kakita-san.
Osaka. I didn't do it.
Oh, shit, you're right.
Umeda, not doing it. Non-stop.
No, no, wait, I was born in Osaka, but now I'm in Kanto
I'm in Tochigi.
Tochigi.
Okay, okay, okay.
I'm sure you're right. I'm sure I'm right.
I'm definitely doing and watching nonstop already.
Which one of you gave Kaki's nostalgic toy as a present to her brother?
The one I wanted to give a present to.
Stalla's brother.
There it is, there it is.
Sorry, sorry, sorry
This is hard.
Why?
My dad loves baseball.
It's the baseball version.
He picked it out for me.
He's your father.
I heard you have a big house.
That's not true.
Where is it?
Well, you have a big house, so if you have that game...
I thought maybe we could have a party at home.
I thought we could play together.
I thought maybe you and Himura could play together.
I think we'll play at home.
I thought maybe the two of us could play together.
Wow, that wasn't me.
That was hard.
It was hard.
No, I wanted to guess.
It could have been me.
I was overthinking it.
Stalla couldn't win her own present.
I'll buy it out of my own pocket.
Well, you can call me when you're ready to play.
Thank you.
I'll play then.
Next time I'm open.
What the hell?
Pickles.
Pickles, pickles, pickles.
pickles
I put my heart and soul into pickling vegetables.
If you marry me, you can eat this every morning
No, no, no, if you marry me...
I thought if I made it
I thought you would be very happy with what I made.
What?
You mean you made it this time?
Or do you have them?
I'll try it.
I'll have a carrot.
Bon appétit!
It's so good!
Well, look how good you're using it. You, huh?
This is good either way... This is difficult...
I'm not saying it's a no-brainer.
I won't do it
No, no, no, you didn't say that just now
So you like pickles? No, no, I don't think I'm saying that much, I like pickles, but if you look at food in general...
You're Mr. Himura, right? But you're kind of austere, like me?
It's not me. It's not me.
He's a bit heavy-handed. I can see why. He's a Matsumura type.
Let's guess who's the Matsumura type and find out... if you marry me, you'll get to eat this every morning.
You're saying this? I'm a yubiki too.
I love it.
I like it a lot.
I can eat this every morning.
I don't know if anyone else eats this in the morning.
If it's nonstop, it's all me, so I'm thinking that since I'm a gourmet and I've seen you eat so much, I'll eat pickles.
I don't think I'm me.
It's Food Himura. It's Food Himura.
I was confused by the sound of rice earlier, but it's Food Himura.
Thank you so much! I'll get this gift... from Himura.
Let's see...
Who prepared these presents?
Who's that?
Oh, it's me!
Is Yamashita's pickles a present for big brother Himura?
I wanted to give him a present.I wanted to give you a gift.
If I did, big brother.
no, no, no, no
I'm sorry
That's so hard
Why?
I've made fried rice for the "Cooking Queen" competition.
I've also made curry for Himura-san's present project, and I've done a lot of cooking.
When I wanted to cook something, I wanted to put my love into it.
It's for this.
I've never made nukazuke before.
I bought some nukazuke and did a lot of research.
I ate this myself.
I haven't eaten it.
Try it. It's delicious.
Really?
I got this out of the store.
No, you used the right ingredients.
It's really good.
Yeah, it was.
It's insanely good.
Yum.
You'd make a great wife.
What is that?
Yes, that's right.
But it's just my personal image.
I don't think she'd eat something with human hands on it.
What do you mean?
Himura-san seems like he'd eat it.
I was hoping you'd eat it and feel my love.
Ah!
That's what I meant. That's why I pickle them every day.
I don't really want to eat rice balls made by others.
That's right.
I'll eat onigiri, too.
What do you mean?
That's right.
Wait... is this about Non-Stop?
Non-stop has nothing to do with it.
It has nothing to do with it.
Okay, okay, okay.
Does it have anything to do with the morning drama?
No, it has nothing to do with morning drama.
It has nothing to do with the morning drama.
I'm not involved in morning drama.
I'm not involved in the morning drama.
By the way, if it was Himura...
I was thinking of making homemade sausages.
I found it on a video site.
He likes sausages.
You look like a sausage.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
I'm sorry. Thank you very much. I'll buy it from you.
Thank you very much.
Great show.
Wow!
Mega heart tipple.
Heart tipple.
I know.
The heart tipple we talked about the other day.
The other day.
It's full of candy.
I'm so excited.
That's totally Southan.
I think it's totally me.
5,000 yen worth of candy bars.
When you grow up, you won't have a chance to buy candy.
So, my teacher, please go buy 5,000 yen worth of something that you know you'll like.
That's really great!
When you grow up, you won't have a chance to buy any candy, will you?
I'm totally buying them.
That's really great.
Look at this yogurt thing.
It's a box, a box of yogurt.
That yogurt thing.
Moroccan fruit yogurt?
It's a box.
That's great.
For $5,000, it's such a great buy.
I mean, they're gonna throw in a heart tipple.
This place is everything now.
But I think it's already me.
Eating equals ice cube.
If this is the dimpled pattern from earlier, it's bad.
I mean, I'm the one who did this to him.
That's the one that really bothers me the most.
This is really from the other night.
I can't believe you don't know what a heart tipple is.
I'd like you to try our heart tipple.
All of you.
Okay? This is a present.
It's one of your presents, so it's okay.
Just a little piece of each of these.
I want you to know how good Heart Chipotle is.
If you've never had it...
Try it.
Isn't it good?
It's so garlicky!
It's such a good snack.
How come no one knows about it?How come I don't know this much?
It's so good!
I'd say this is number one.
I don't know if I'm good at this.
I'm sure it's fine.
There's no reason why it should be me.
If there were more Umaibo, it would be like me.
One summer
I ate about 260 of them.
That's a lot.
Everyone knows that.
I love candy bars, too.
I love it.
Didn't they call me "Mr. Kawayaku"?
No, they don't.
I don't know, but they do.
I don't have that one.
Me neither.
I mean, from a relationship standpoint, it's perfect, but I'm the one who likes shiitake and stuff.
It's better that way.
I don't know if she gets that.
Look, I'm fine.
I'm 100% okay with it.
I can get this present, big brother.
Who bought this present for me?
Who?
Oh, there it is.
Is it tight?
Heart tipple is the key already, isn't it?
Surprising, isn't it?
I didn't expect that.
I thought I'd have more lace handkerchiefs and stuff.
Tough.
Let's hear it.
It's a tight candy set.
So it's a present for you, then?
I wanted to give you a present.
Big brother Nimura.
What?
Mr. Himura...
Don't do that.
I knew it!
No, no, no, no, don't put that in.
What's wrong with this?
It only took me a second to decide.
If it's for Mr. Himura...
I thought candy would be the best.
And the Heart Chipotle...
I'd never seen them before.
I thought, "Oh, this has Stara-san in it.
I was so happy.
I chose all of them.
That's right.
She really went to buy them!
I'm so happy!
She even put in the ones you mentioned.
I knew it! It's Mr. Himura!
I'm sorry.
Himura, who missed it...
He paid 5,000 yen to make up for it.
Did you eat? I had a heart tipple just now.
They had a smaller one.
I got one for myself.
They were so good!
I want to do this forever. We're just having fun, that's all.
We're just having fun!
I'm not going to say "nonstop" anymore.
What's this little thing?
What's this?
Makeup?
It's a men's version of makeup that makes your nose look taller and adds shading.
If you're feeling a little swollen today, I recommend a natural shade of makeup.
This item has recently been attracting attention as a men's cosmetic, and it should be easy to use even for those who don't usually wear makeup.
It gives a clean, transparent, and blood-colored look.
Which is it, Mr. Nimura?
But I'm going to go out on a limb here and say that, for example, when I see you on Nonstop.
I look pale, especially under my eyes in the mornings.
I'm often told I have dark circles, but it's business as usual.
I think that's why they say, "Mr. Himura, maybe you should make these areas look sharper.
You know the makeup we used to do for the summer season?
I wonder if it's just a little bit of tweaking or something, but it gives a sense of cleanliness, transparency, and blood coloring.
Transparency? Blood color?
That's me. But it's clean.
I guess you're right about the transparency.
Not even cleanliness. It's sad.
Only the color of blood. Only the color of blood.
I don't know if I'd want you to use it on me, but I wouldn't either, if I said that.
I don't know, it's a nonstop morning show, so I don't think it's a message that says, "Please show more color, transparency, and cleanliness.
But if she says she's swollen, that means it's Mr. Himura. When he comes out with his face like that on Gourmet, I think he's super fat.
I agree. Who's this?
Is this Miki?
No? I don't think she's fat.
You don't think I'm fat, you just don't think I'm fat.
I'm not skinny. I'm skinny.
Then what am I? I'm skinny!
Who's that skinny guy? Maybe Kiyomiya.
I think so... Kiyomiya?
Mr. Himura here. I'm Himura, the big brother who can get you this present.
Who bought this for me?
Who did it?
I'm sure it's Mr. Himura. He'll say "swollen".That's why I'm sure Mr. Himura will say that Kiyomiya is swollen.
He'll say it, and then I'll see the "he's fat" part.
I'm going to do it. I'm going to do it now.
Bananaman, who constructed a stupid theory... is Cicada's present for Brother Himura a hand?
I wanted to give her a present.
Shimoda.
I was wrong. This is nonstop? Non-stop?
Non-stop!
It's nonstop.
I watch Non-Stop a lot.
But when I watched it, I always thought Shimoda-san was so handsome.
His nose is so beautiful.
I thought he'd look even better if he had a little more luster here and there.
That's right.
I told you that before, didn't I?
Now Semia can do Shimoda's makeup.
Like this?
That's right.
That way it'll look nice.
It looks like a Leo Green job on the first floor of a department store.
It looks like that.
The wide one here, with the flowers.
Do men wear makeup these days?
Yes, men and women can use this.
Women can use it too?
Yes, for example, you said you were worried about dark circles here.
If you put a little bit under your eyes...
The lamé will make the dark circles disappear.
Does it have lame?
There's a lot of lame.
Doesn't it look a little weird?
No, it's not.
I'm a guy, so I'm a little uncomfortable with lame.
Is it normal now?
It's a little bit watery and glittery.
It's not that glittery?
And your face...
You're going to do this, too?
The face, and the lips, that's what girls do.
Then they do it.
It makes the lips look a little more beautiful.
They look different?
They look better.
It looks better, doesn't it?
Yes, they look better.
What? Oh, my God.
I don't know what's wrong with me.
The blood in there, it's white now, and it's clean.
I swear, to the naked eye, it's nothing like that.
That's great.
I feel so much better.
I hope you don't think I feel better.
Are you okay?
Are you okay with nonstop?
I'm fine with nonstop.
I'm sorry. I made a mistake.
So Shimohara went to buy a present with his own money to make up for missing the present.
Let's guess the last one!
Obuzan!
That's a real curveball!
What's this?
Scary!
I want to smell the bamboo!
What the hell?
Is this a dud?
This is a banana flower.
I thought it would be heavy to receive something tangible from me, with whom I have only a short relationship, so I decided to give something that would be eaten and gone.
Can you eat this?
I looked up "banana" and found that the language of flowers fits perfectly, so I chose this one.
Language of flowers
I didn't write it down.
If you write it down, they'll know.
That's how they'll know.
I see.
I've prepared some unseasoned, pre-cooked food, just in case.
Here it is.
It doesn't look like bamboo shoots.
Look at this.
What's this?
Is it good?
Bon appétit!
Oh, my God!
It's so good!
The more you open it, the more astringent it gets.
That's Mr. Himuro for food.
I'm sure he's right. Me, me, me.
This is Yumeki, right?
I'm the one with all the tricky stuff.
No, but I'm only involved with this for a short time.
Oh, goki!
You're insane!
No, I don't know. All goki are insane.
No, I'm sane.
I don't even know if they're intelligent or not.
Even Inoue knows about this stuff.
I see... I guess they know.
You'll get this present.
And the last guess goes to Nimura.
Who bought the banana flower?
Who will it be?Who could it be?
There he is!
You guessed it!
Inoue's banana flower.
I wonder which brother won it.
The one I wanted to give a present to...
Himara's brother.
I won!
Thank you.
But why did you give this to Himara?
It's pretty tricky.
But I wanted something that would really go away.
I had a lot of candidates.
I want to erase the fact that I gave it to you.
I want to erase that fact that I gave it to you.
That's all I can hear right now.
I don't want it to go away.
When you're giving a gift, you want to give them what they want.
I want to give them what they want.
But we don't have much of a relationship yet.
I don't want to give them something they don't want.
I think we have a really, really deep relationship.
I'm the only one.
That's a little disconcerting.
Think more.
So how did you end up with this?
That's right.
Nogizaka's color is purple.
It's a purple flower.
This one...
Because it's purple and you're Bananaman.
It's the language of flowers.
The language of flowers.
"style" and "Kanroku"...
Fugaku Kanroku.
It's Mr. Himura.
I know.
I'm going to go out on a limb here.
Even if I eat one, it's still hard.
Really?
You don't sing at all.
What? Inoue's eating it?
What's wrong?
This is it.
Why?
Second round of Banatu's national tour is now open!
Hello, I'm Rika Sato. Today's haircut is straight because I'm wearing this uniform for the first time at Nogicho.
I also curled my bangs today. What kind of hair style do you like?
Please subscribe to our channel. Bye bye bye!
by H.